{
    "subject": "resource/Yul_Brynner",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Yul Brynner",
    "human_readable": "The label of Yul Brynner is Yul Brynner.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9174837470054626,
            "question": "Who is Yul Brynner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935017585754395,
            "question": "What is the name of Yul Brynner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8587949872016907,
            "question": "What is Yul Brynner known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8104209303855896,
            "question": "Is Yul Brynner a real person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7810366153717041,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about Yul Brynner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7622151374816895,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Yul Brynner's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7289968132972717,
            "question": "Where was Yul Brynner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7211006283760071,
            "question": "What is Yul Brynner's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6556281447410583,
            "question": "What year was Yul Brynner born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6500260233879089,
            "question": "Has Yul Brynner won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Yul Brynner is Yul Brynner.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7873_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Yul Brynner born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7873_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Yul Brynner's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7873_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Yul Brynner born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7873_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7873_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently refer to the individual as Yul Brynner, supporting the triple that the label of Yul Brynner is indeed Yul Brynner."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}